it already did watch the old scope these
they all have you okay where it's
working it's working
wait do they like it help you put it on
Twitter right like you click to Twitter
did you pick the Twitter button I mean
I'm only here did I click the Twitter
button
I'm only here through Twitter ask the
God no but you have to click the button
to share please leave 22 people already
well they could be notification salon
Eric can you tell me if I click the
Twitter button
it's on Twitter okay cool cool we were
just talking about how well this car
drives yeah this is an a chord yeah this
is the awkward it's really really smooth
there there
we don't use the proper
ready like anymore can buy one this
isn't like today this is like these ooks
yeah right you can't say it's answers
doesn't make any sense that's it guys
we're driving down to Campbell to pick
up some servers before our presentation
I got us a great deal on servers man I
found George you destroyed oh my god I'm
sorry
Wow that works it works its own this car
needs 2x torque the torque is a little
weak
you know our Civic has 2x torque
it's very nice but new models so good
nice hair George Wow oh yeah you did
this but yeah we're going on a like
experiments to finish fast so we'll
increase research productivity
yes yes if I get investigated
yeah we have a paper trail oh yeah we
gotta stop because we gotta keep
presentation 4:30 by the way guys
yeah we're dropping cash on servers
who's doing it that's like the time Jake
pull up on the Lambo with pennies no he
didn't stage thing yeah that's why it
was crazy
cancel the product announcement well
chase being CEO is worked worse fake
news than oh I don't know Paul I have
some political examples and we don't
believe it I mean absolutely we don't
discuss politics now we discuss politics
a lot we just don't judge people let's
say no judgement guys the world needs a
lot less judgement and a lot more love
the county last element looks like a
safe space he's all about the luck yeah
it's Commons the safe space for everyone
yeah can we also mention we're bringing
back the mobile store store file the
4:30 in Mountain View we're doing this
presentation yeah if you guys want to
drop by I think we'll be done around
5:00 we'll be standing outside the
Computer History Museum with the mobile
store come look we'll do an IRL man one
day we'll have so many followers we'll
do like flash mobs oh that'll be
but this car drives amazingly yeah and
now there's a charge in his shoes be
fixed
yeah we just we have the charge against
you on the way back from camping it's
$150 a ticket yeah I know
are you serious I know well you know I
feel like on this right so no no but
we'll we'll bring the mobile store
outside well we do have a comma meetup
right there in the park exactly if
anyone shows up we'll show you this back
you can check out our end a cord yeah
this thing drives so great yeah the way
back from camping we hit the charging
issue oh that's right and you were
really fun I was so bummed not to have
it that really like turn my mood or out
well and then it hit me that I walk 90
miles
oh my god
oh my gosh
scared to hit the gas pedal um yeah but
this car does need to x-torq so if
anyone's got that 2x4 c'mon our Civic
has to explore but if anyone's got that
2x Torquemada out there for the Accord
conspirator sponsored by yerba Oh
I feel like you always are drinking at
your Vermont a in the periscope they can
sponsor soldier who can wear this to a
party dad the stork is hitting it right
here yeah it just feels better with the
2x4 guys we got to do torque more
someone just said I'll trade you torque
months so you have a court or poon gym
it I would trade Civic for quad for
court or quad so someone just said I'll
trade you in for the sip of the Civic
Tour c'mon yeah but do they have a court
or club do you have a chord I would
trade a court I would trade center for
Court
like at that point like here's the thing
about the tart pot it's only unsafe in
the hands of news in progress they said
if someone's good enough to figure out
the award or not like I'm not worried
about you also having Pacific tour I
have 20 18 accord no they don't have
much torque mod torque was so hard
exhibit my baby ref maybe maybe 20
people in the world get to tour pot well
maybe at Hell fish is the one for us I
don't know if those guys can do torque
torque one is hard accurate torquemada's
easier but civic torque mode requires
dumping the firmware and like I kind of
told people half how to do it in my code
blue talk but it's really hard maybe you
should do a live periscope of how to do
it you're trying to trick me Scotty 4:30
p.m. Pacific Standard Time yeah we're
dropping a new product we got a
presentation prepared yeah it's gonna be
crazy it's gonna mine they're not on the
wheel this way cuz I got driver
monitoring what it's looking at me
yeah look away
there you go keep looking away oh yeah
yeah it's gonna be scope we're gonna put
it we're gonna lie to you but we're not
gonna ask beg for forgiveness that's
right do you think it was gonna ask yeah
I mean maybe they've seen my stuff about
now we don't ask no just like do it like
can stop you know keep it like under
your breast pocket that's right you know
why this character is doing the right
thing when nobody's watching and
periscoping that we'll be doing the
right thing nobody will watch no we
already don't hear this thing about
characters it's a beautiful quote
character is doing the right thing when
nobody is watching characters are doing
the right thing like character that your
characters are doing the right thing
Wow so you tell me if I got a piece of
paper with some characters on it they're
doing the right thing even when nobody's
watching that's good yeah you can do the
right thing and put some characters on
paper you don't I'm saying that's right
I love language man you see George
Carlin talking about how he loves
language George Carlin is that damn
Carlin's brother no I'm gonna be cool oh
yeah no George Cohen was a comedian
back in the day
rolled in his grave if you saw the world
that I you guys on doesn't way better
than a onus now like just in general I
love this car
this car as a car I this is my favorite
of the comic cars by far I drove the
Santa Fe I know I was saying good things
about you and I yeah but somebody is
nice from a like torque and latency
perspective but from like a car
perspective and I kind of hated it yeah
well it's just so big if it were smaller
it be I like it but I like this car
anymore this is this is an incredible 0
to 60 times and my Benz yeah but your
Benz is a boat yeah I know but my Benz
had like a 400 horsepower engine it's a
blocky video that's the worst
purrs go sucks okay the Lexus is you can
also download more torque for this car
down a little more horsepower for this
car um but no it like honestly this car
doesn't need more horsepower because if
you slam on the gas at the light you're
already getting tire stick we can I
block box yeah you can block whoever you
want fit if they piss you off you can
block okay I block people block resists
sometimes we have wrasses Scott Walker
gotta try the Chevy's maybe Chevy's brow
we have Cadillac it's I I don't like the
Cadillac like this car I mean they like
this car better than the Cadillac I like
the Honda and the Hyundai the best no
but this car is by far my favorite
I wish we had Torquemada and I wish we
had stop and go and then we can do the
awareness tour in this car you so me
atopic stopping though no or stop and go
oh oh we're gonna start slowing down for
turns once we ship slow down for turns
then it's gonna suck if you don't have
kama stopping up yeah is it one slow
down returns for you actually
I think these buttons are on can we
could probably smooth them maybe
probably slow the speed down I know
we're spamming the resume
this is the Honda Accord 2018 2018
latitude yeah
2018 2.0 tour and this car has crazy
horsepower Jeff
like I said I can get tires with of like
as far as a front-wheel drive car goes
you're not really gonna do that much
better I don't know what is the fastest
0 to 60 on a front-wheel drive car
like I don't think it can like what's
the fastest it can be but you know the
problem the funnel drive cars right they
just press around 60 times well no you
um your car leans back when you're
accelerating right and then you don't
have downforce on the front wheels
anymore and then people who put spoilers
on front-wheel drive cars you're
literally doing the opposite of what you
want you got a rear-wheel drive car
right you're getting downforce on the
back wheels that you can accelerate and
then for a lot of cars obviously great -
this is - will this was - it was peril
drive car yeah like I don't know what
the best 0 to 6 this can do 0 to 60 I
think like five seconds
it's like 5.3 stock and it feels fast
yeah it does feel fast all you need is
wider wheels ok I'm not sure wider
wheels help you I mean they probably do
but now you have even less downforce
right like your psi on wider wheels is
gonna be lower all right but basic
physics if you have the same amount of
weight
I guess you have a heavier bar needs to
transfer more energy and put a spoiler
on the front does some guys have that
baby more weight with a giant battery
now while no charm or weight helps you
because the problem is more weight is
now you need to transfer more energy to
the road right like blow about how much
energy you can transfer to the road how
quick
like if this car had a thousand
horsepower engine I'm not sure it would
even accelerate that much faster at
least must stop like the zero to thirty
part of it
the 30 to 60 you could probably give it
to the horseman you're not gonna
continue to get tires with Vietnamese
stop for a second zero to sixty four F
cars
everything we got 74 driving there are
so blocky is it so Pocky
oh man that smoke
those who does raise a type of thing
test sound like crazy but I mean those
Tesla's that have to crazy zero to sixty
s are all are all the drive or even like
yes first up for front-wheel drive cars
but with slicks oh it selects a careless
are there any street-legal from hill
drive cars that are sub floor
it has us to do you tell us of some
three but yeah those are all the drive
and a heavy car which again I don't know
if that helps apparently still blocking
what sleek could someone look it up
what's that what's the best front-wheel
drive 0-60
I wonder if it really is this car like a
civic type-r Semak type archive or is
the best is that does that choose civic
type-r
this is I mentioned to you three is four
point seven yeah yeah do you taste 4.7
lb cuantos p3 is Oh a three somf hades
overdrive yes I'm victim ik both they
for it I make both okay all Quattro I
don't know I know the ones you can rent
from silver car for over this we're
gonna go we were gonna go Madeline I
we're gonna go drive to the snow I can't
talk to your phone
I shouldn't use my phone when I Drive a
periscope no Civic type-r is low five
seconds there - six a five second second
it's not some time
really
I could do a 4.9
maybe there's a tuning for it surname is
hot sounds made up
it's Jeff I'm like Britney Spears I made
my name up before I was famous that's
right yeah yes I know Britney me yeah of
course you did I think no it's not I
think it's a real name I mean you know
Christina Aguilera didn't make her name
off what the hell kind of name is that
Christina Aguilera is that is to me guy
no no I'm pretty sure it's a bigger name
I don't think I guess her sister is
Jamie's Jamie Lynn Spears Spears any I'm
sure there's like but I don't think
there's any other mass-market
I mean it would be one of these like
hi-spec Japanese probably but like
Lancer Evo's are four-wheel drive
I don't know like can you get like an m5
and know those rear-wheel drive even the
ones that are affordable
do you know what we're going this way
okay gotta get to Campbell thank you I'm
trying to be on top of it with the bots
just gotta get rid of it bad bot iscope
got any questions this question our this
things are driving without a
disengagement now for like 50 get
disengagement so I was careful you're
going to feel like Silicon Valley's
crumbling or is it just us but I think
everyone feels that way about it you
know our get everyone's business
America's crumbling so we're doing well
in the world that's what I'm gonna find
on my grand adventure no oh god that was
yesterday I'm triggered did you go oh
goodness that was a terrible thing I
won't poor what goes on at the Folsom
Street Fair but it shouldn't be on a
public street and it shouldn't be in the
middle of the deck you can remove any
one of those things and then it's okay
yeah but in the middle of the day
there's like like nine year olds out the
middle of the day it's fine public
street is a little weird but if you
weren't on a public street or like 11p
I'm like all right fine
you know all the kids are asleep no cuz
then they're trying to sleep and they're
getting you you know who's loud but like
okay there's loud stuff occasionally at
night
I'm like you know you if you're in that
kind of area all right like think of the
Castro don't try these crazy jam-packed
people yes and that's all cool because
just nighttime
no no cashes us no prizes listen during
the day try these a little bit better
it's a little bit more corporatized oh
now we're just getting to the falls
no no I'm triggered by the Folsom Street
back it's too much man
it's a new product new or just a
reimagined current product hey man
everything is ever see Avengers 3 which
is the Avengers 3 of products we want to
see the third spider-man before it's
spider-man how many spider-man's were
there waiting and they weren't even like
new spider-man they were all the
spider-man origin story yeah I got overs
by him it was the Tobey Maguire one it
was that like other one with her like
Tobey Maguire and whoever played the
girl weren't pretty so we're gonna make
pretty people play them who did they use
it I think tell you the buyers totally
pretty
oh my god no the old like the original
spider-man total Maguire and who's that
girl not pretty
wait who was the original Mary Jane I
don't know I was hoping but wires
attract I think so oh yeah first and
done here's the doors oh yeah then the
new Spider that the second spider-man
came out and they used attractive people
ooh they use I don't know but they were
good-looking
like Tokyo glaring Kirsten does are
perfect for each other they're both like
fives as far as Hollywood goes I'm sure
person actually extremely yeah Kim
Kardashian - Ian's good luck in there
been transparent Ian Purple Panda what
Purple Panda
they used Emma Stone yeah see now we're
getting pretty girls right who's the guy
who's the guy that you know was the guy
I'm not talking about the most recent
spider-man or eBay where they had like
Iron Man in it and stuff is that was
that spider-man or we get back to me I
can't believe I'm talking about
superhero movie rebates so terribly jus
Garfield oh yeah yeah yeah you do know
that is she was I think using the social
network
she's Sabourin no I don't know oh I
remember
yeah
social networks y'all real Facebook
guys when I was there this in turn was
like mr. Zuckerberg at like TV yeah you
know that's Google real Google
Facebook at gjs - well no they call them
like social Fridays or something mr.
Zuckerberg can you like tell us like the
story of Facebook like what was the real
story oh wait crazy is Google has also
like scrubbed references to that from
the internet yeah like I tried to find
it I couldn't yeah and they're like hey
a happy happy event the guys
Tobey Maguire filets me I support that
movie they could get the throw to Elijah
Wood I would be okay with that
oh yeah yeah hey Elijah if you're
listening let us know
Orlando Bloom would make me look stupid
yeah the guy just doesn't look sour
looks smart he looks pretty he looks
like like uh like on a sculpture and
then he talks yeah these people still
relevant
No Hollywood is crumbly I've been an
ugly soul stone article with Johnny Depp
it was so depressed honey jab that man
is just done Johnny Depp was eaten like
likely lately pirates went to his head
pirates won the game was great back like
Pulp Fiction and stuff yeah but then
pirates comes out no no Pirates of the
Caribbean one he was pirates can be one
was the great movie actress that was the
end Antonio Epps correct any made like a
creepy Charlie and the Chocolate Factory
yeah there is that terrible singularity
movie he just like and then they kept
trying to make weight he was in Pulp
Fiction
wasn't it pop fiction said no Jackson
was in Pulp Fiction who was the other
guys giant app wasn't it
no that was like how he got his start
he was an Alice in Wonderland that's
right oh that was bad never mind Johnny
Depp was great Wow think if possible I
haven't even a lower opinion of trying
to he's never been in anything good how
did that guy get famous like what did he
get famous from he's pretty and he was
an I think price of the Caribbean was
real is that really it was that it's
like debut movie no this is bad
celebrity memory history our absolutely
Nightmare on Elm Street
Oh was his first 21 jumps you never saw
it never saw it touch it I did see 21
Jump Street but that was like way later
to get to a straighter we should look
and see where the servers are guys we're
going to buy servers yeah we're going if
you ask more questions will answer
questions instead of bad celebrity
gossip our everyone let's go well we
haven't really driven that much weight
someone's someone's worried that him
blocking on BOTS know they're all BOTS
the ones who repeat and put a little
emoji emoji those are all BOTS
why are we buying service because we
need servers to run Maps
we have a little cluster which makes the
maps did new good ml KY accept offer
this is our new good mmm elk I haven't
you written up yo get this model that
was me yeah he also does a little bit of
social media but it's a little much for
him so you know anymore so smart I don't
ml and hype hype yeah we're doing hype
today it's gonna be crazy
response ignite is my second part I am
really yeah coffee
wow it was secret better ml coroner I'm
not know about better yeah different new
model is awesome great set for it thank
you no no you see the thing about anti
hype and hype is they're the same thing
you know you guys know about the thesis
and the antithesis of a synthesis for Co
or whoever those Deborah do whatever
those assholes were get it always live
in a postmodern world
yes
I wish people who we're delivering yeah
that was a totally a mistake I miss
click then if you were blocked pointing
out a Bob but you got back in which is
the good news it's a mouse slip
I wish to figure out where we're going
laughs it is I know I got called out for
not reading out the comments but we're
not just close know we are close
14 minutes 14 minutes oh that's it yeah
we're so close
when I take the stereo let's go around
the truck
[Music]
well Gilroy the garlic capital here No
exit 12 this one yeah good thing we
check if they reach s it's the garlic
capital of the US did you know that they
have garlic ice cream in Gilroy
damn do they have like the world's
largest hamster wheel - probably cool I
love roadside attractions ya know this
this self-driving awareness - we got two
more roadside attractions the the yeah
one of the greatest roadside attractions
was little America will American Nevada
and we got girls club it was not Nevada
what America was into Prescott no it
wasn't it was the full earth way before
Nebraska was like date day one or day
two no no it was right after Salt Lake
City yeah Ben yeah after so execution
nowhere Nevada is right all right it was
after Salt Lake City yeah but it wasn't
in Nebraska might have been in Wyoming
it was in Miami yeah yeah I do I agree
that it was pre Nebraska yes we didn't
really do roadside attractions Nebraska
we were tired of trying to get to
Chicago he's wait Chicago we didn't go
to Chicago yeah we did we ended it yeah
yeah
now well so what was the day maybe
nebraska's what we just drove through to
get to Kansas I mean know if we went to
Nebraska we did omotchama
we got good stuff that's pre kiddo
that's like in the same level as Kansas
that was after Kansas City that was
after kids yeah we can just check the
back of my shirt
hey great shirt oh yeah do it again yeah
it was fun I also want to go down south
I just kind of want to go down south
really no I also want to check out like
the Texas settings I've never been to
you know Houston have no zoning laws I'm
down I'm down to go deep south do it you
know let's do it let's meet some
southerners same I'd rather take ya
court though
no no in the deep south of food and
better with a bigger santa fe no we look
like like like liberals from the Pacific
Northwest that's what we are progressive
we all believe in progress like better
models and and you know slowing down for
turns and saying all the great kind of
progress that's progress
stay on 85 south 6.1 miles to Winchester
Boulevard did George tell you guys he
got it the new phone oh yeah you like my
new phone Apple guys actually I went to
the Apple store and long story short
they wouldn't let me buy the phone it's
not what you're thinking
but you know they wouldn't let me buy
the phone so I bought a case instead and
told people on the phone yeah
does new product support little big
model new product is going to support
everything last products points
they're the same codebase it's a better
product we're excited for you guys if
you see there's a better product I think
yeah yeah it's more polished yeah you'll
see and it comes in a box that sounds
I'm leaking this week's you're leaking a
lot I know
hey revin dropped some bar from Comikaze
drop some bars from Kamikaze what were
we
I know and did come in a box but this is
a better box
all I'm thinking of the only bar that
I'm thinking of it was something like
three albums when I was 29 that's when
my career blew
I'd rather be 80 year old me than 40
year old you come back to MGK yeah
that's right
kamikaze bars I got a couple of mentions
still I don't have any manners I got it
you got a couple of ghost writers bunch
of these kids that don't actually matter
Oh Oh mmm for the win yeah
all right Scopus maybe I'll leave you
guys we'll leave you guys we're gonna
remember every tell everybody product
launch 4:30 p.m. today 4:00 p.m. 4:30 I
think you're on at 4:00
no 4:30 best with the website sad oh
really
we're gonna keep you guys up to date
yeah they don't follow us on Twitter
what are you doing follow us on Twitter
that's how Logan Paul talks get sure to
click that like and subscribe button
what happened to Logan Paul that guy
fell off hard all right all right